<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KKS Suppliers Club</title>
    <link>https://kksclub.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on KKS Suppliers Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 23:02:15 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kksclub.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://kksclub.com/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 23:02:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kksclub.com/about-us/</guid>
      <description>The KKS Company KKS is a online overseas sourcing platform.
 We host a combination of platform solutions offering wholesale both B2B and B2B2C online business models for various top SME merchants which is a fair marketplace that removes inefficiency and cost resulting in the best value for merchants with improved margin.
 Over the past 4 years KKS has evolved to be a trusted and professional platform to help overseas suppliers sell their products to China online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preferential Policies</title>
      <link>https://kksclub.com/preferential-policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 22:15:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kksclub.com/preferential-policies/</guid>
      <description>The Chinese government has revamped the guidelines to support cross border E-commerce For cross-border E-commerce, the tax rate was lowered from 11.2% to 9.1% for ordinary cosmetics, and from 25.53% to 23.05% for high-end cosmetics，from 15% to 13% for food and medicine; and from 25% to 20% for textiles, leather garments, and electrical appliances.  Low cost market entry for testing and assortment optimization. No extra sales/operational costs. Flexible settlement options: weekly or monthly in home currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two business models to jump in China market</title>
      <link>https://kksclub.com/two-business-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 16:41:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kksclub.com/two-business-models/</guid>
      <description>Fresh Brands If your brand has lower awareness in China and intent to touch base with China market In the KFC Model the merchant can put the product in KKS overseas warehouses. This is relatively an easier model to test new products in the market. The merchant will take responsibility to deliver the products into the KFC warehouse where from all aspects of delivery will be handled by KKS. Hence businesses which have low brand awareness but intent to test China market could use this model.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>